Priyanshi Sachan

695/30 Prakruti Empire, Near Satyam Apartments, Gorwa | Vadodara, 390016 |

Phone: 08200147440

E-Mail: priyanshiwork18@gmail.com

Summary

I have undergone training and internship for MERN stack development and consider myself fit for new projects. I'm a teamworker and will communicate with my peers with sincerity. I want to gain more experience while working on small and big projects. I have a better hand in frontend development but can also make my way through backend development. I would like to bring value to any organization I work with while also analyzing myself for the areas of improvement.

Experience

March 2022 to Present

Intership | ReactJs Developement Intern | IWebCode

- Developed user interfaces with modern JavaScript frameworks, HTML5 and CSS3.
- · Worked on projects focused on React and typescript.
- Learned new technologies/frameworks such as React-Hook-Form, React Native, Firebase, Strapi.
- Troubleshot and debugged code ensuring compatibility with devices, browsers, and operating systems.
- Studied basic project requirements with assigned technical lead and planned development strategies.
- Designed and implemented web components across new and existing designs.

September 2021 to December 2021

Intership | Web Developer Intern | Devtown

- Developed user interfaces with modern JavaScript frameworks, HTML5 and CSS3.
- Worked on eCommerce maintenance and management for client websites.

- Troubleshot and debugged code ensuring compatibility with devices, browsers, and operating systems.
- Studied basic project requirements with assigned technical lead and planned development strategies.
- Designed and implemented web components across new and existing designs.

June 2021 to August 2021

Intership | Sales and Marketing Intern | Ifortis Corporate

- · Sales funnel
- Creation of key visuals & presentations
- Promotion: Integrated Marketing Communication
- Segmentation & Targeting
- Marketing & sales strategy
- Consumer Behavior
- Managed customer expectations and helped navigate sales processes

Education

- Maharaja Sayajirao University, Vadodara [Present]
 Post Graduate Diploma in Computer Applications (PGDCA)
- Bansthali Vidyapith Tonk, Rajasthan [May 2022]
 Bachelor of Arts Computer Applications, Economics, Sociology
 Graduate degree with Distinction with CGPA of 8.94/10
- Bright Day School Vadodara [May 2019]

High School graduation (std. XII) Commerce

Skills

- Full-stack development
- HTML
- CSS
- ReactJs
- TypeScript
- Firebase and Strapi
- JavaScript
- Git and Github
- ChakraUI and Bootstrap
- Node.js, Express
- Mongodb, MySql, NestJs

Achievements

Successfully completed training and internship for Full Stack Web Development with <u>Devtown</u>.

Successfully completed Basic Web Dev with HTML, CSS, Javascript bootcamp, Basic Web Dev with Javascript and ReactJs bootcamp, and Basic Netflix Clone bootcamp. These camps were launched and guided by <u>Devtown</u>. Received recognition from institutes like Google Developer Student Clubs, BIT Mersa and Google Developers Group, Ranchi.

Projects

· React Hook Form with Firebase and Strapi

The form was created using React hook form library, typescript and bootstrap, it accepts user information and uploads it to firebase and straps database. The user can upload their resume and sent in data. It also involves react captcha verification, which verifies the data and then sends it to the database or else provides errors.

React Native app with signIn and signUp functionality

The app enables user to register as a new user, login with existing account and also signIn with their google account. Upon successful login the user can explore posts by other accounts, create and explore their own posts and explore more. The user data is stored on firebase cloud firestore. The app was made using React native components and Expo.

E-commerce app

This website enables users to browse through multiple products available, add them to cart and also enable payment configured with Razorpay paymenet gateway. The website is created using React ChakraUI, MongoDb, Nodejs and Express (MERN stack).

Impact website UI development

This project was created using ReactJs, Typescript and ChakraUI. The main aim was to practice UI development using these technologies. The website has a hero component, carousel, video modal and multi-level drawer. It is responsive for all screens.

Interests and Extra curricular activities

- I like playing outdoor and indoor games such as basketball, kabaddi. Also have participated in inter school and inter college competitions.
- Volunteered in college teams for organizing college level events.

Additional Information

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/priyanshi-sachan-17b73b207

Github: https://github.com/priyanshiisingh/